app-authority.com 2018-09-02

# AppAuthority.com

## Privacy Policy

Welcome to App Authority. We know you care about how your information is collected, used and shared. This notice describes what we do to protect your privacy. By using any App Authority website or application, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined below. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so you should visit often to review any changes.

### Your Privacy Is Important

We regard our customers' privacy as one of our top priorities and have taken great efforts to ensure that your privacy is protected with the highest degree of safety and security. The App Authority website provides you with listings and/or offers on behalf of third parties that we think may be useful to you. We have no responsibility for the Privacy Policy of third party advertisers, and should you have any questions, we ask that you contact third parties directly. If for some reason we are required by law to disclose your private information to an outside party, we will notify you of our obligation before disclosing such information.

### The Information We Collect

Visitors requesting any service, whether for trial purposes or for sale, sometimes choose to give us information, such as their names, email addresses, mailing addresses, payment information and other similar information. In addition, our servers store answers and information you choose to give us.   
In addition, we may record anonymous data about your use of the site, including your internet protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time. This information is used for internal analytics, the results of which are used to improve the application. We may store this information for as long as we feel appropriate.

### Why We Collect Private Information

Any information we collect will be used to: 1) deliver the services requested, 2) communicate with our visitors and members to facilitate delivery of the services they requested, 3) maintain a customer database which will be used for in-house business operations, and 4) market the products and services of our third party advertisers. Purchasing information that is collected is only used to bill the user for the services they choose to purchase.  
From time to time, we will use customer contact information to send the user information about our company and the services we offer. Users may opt-out of receiving any contact from us in any form if they choose to do so by following the unsubscribe instructions via e-mail.

### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser so that our systems recognize you. If you want to change your cookie settings, you can usually do so by clicking the "Help" button on your browser.

### Choice/Opt-Out Policy

Our website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time. From time to time, we may elect to contact you by phone, email, fax, regular mail, or to alert you of problems with your account, announcements of new services, specials, etc. If you wish not to be contacted in any way, please inform us of your request via e-mail.

### Conditions of Use

If you choose to visit any App Authority websites or applications, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Notice and our Conditions of Use. If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy please contact us at support@App-Authority.com.
